PAULDIN BEBLA

7048 Hollow Lake Way, San Jose, CA 95120 • (408) 427-7227 • pbebla@scu.edu

Objective:

I am a motivated, graduating Computer Science student seeking to contribute as well as gain technical experience and skills. I have over five years of computer and networking experience in hardware, software, and customer support.

Education:

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science GPA: 3.676

Master of Science in Computer Science and Engineering (Expected 2021)

Santa Clara University, Santa Clara, CA

Technical Skills:

- Macintosh, Windows, and Linux platforms
- Programming Languages: C/C++,HTML CSS,Python,SQL,Assembly,PHP,Swift,Java
- Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint
- Macintosh servers and databases
- Network switches, routers and firewalls
- Chatbots using JSON APIs, Verilog
- iOS and Android Apps with Video, Forms

Work Experience:

Business Analyst Intern (Full Time)

Cisco

June 2018 – September 2018

Milpitas, CA

- Understand Cisco's security technology to enhance and better simplify their message to customers.
- Compare and contrast Cisco's security messaging with their competitors.
- Evaluate and analyze how to improve overall security messaging to attract a broader audience.
- Use HTML to correct formatting, font, links, and images for altered Cisco communities pages.

Media Systems Assistant (Part Time)

September 2017 - Present

Santa Clara University

Santa Clara, CA

- Set-up of various technologies for educational and/or administration needs.
- Provide instructional technology support and troubleshooting to faculty and staff.
- Process and follow through daily with customer service orders.
- Train co-workers as well manage daily assignments.

Computer and Network Technician (Part Time)

Computer Works International

August 2016 - Present

San Jose, CA

- Provide end-user desktop support, application installation, and training.
- Apple OS server, security firewalls, and ShoreTel VoIP phone system maintenance.
- Modify and maintain FileMaker Pro database and computer backup systems.
- On-call for emergency and weekend support.

Cat6 Wiring Installations

July 2013 - July 2016

San Jose, CA

Computer Works International

- Assisted in installing Cat6 Ethernet wiring throughout multiple floors.
- Installed a network rack, patch panel, and routed wires through the ceilings and walls.
- Maintained and repaired wiring as needed using test and certification equipment.

Teacher's Assistant

August 2015 - May 2016

San Jose, CA

Bellarmine College Preparatory

- Provided support to the teacher of the Digital Video Production class.
- Provided IT support by setting up video and other equipment to prepare for class.
- Filed, graded classwork, maintained organization and cleanliness of classroom.

Leadership:

Voted Hurdle Team Leader of Track and Field in Spring 2016 season at Bellarmine high school.
Helped coach coordinate practice and lead by example during leadership.

Volunteer Experience:

After-School Tutor

August 2015-June 2016

San Jose, CA

- Saint Frances Cabrini Elementary School
 - Assisted 5th 8th grade students with math homework and test preparation.
 - Worked with students to increase interest in learning.